purelyhosting.com 2015-05-10

# Privacy Policy - Purely Hosting

We, PurelyHosting.com LLC., are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you. By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## We are committed to protecting your privacy.

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This privacy policy applies to [www.purelyhosting.com](http://www.purelyhosting.com/) owned and operated by PurelyHosting.com LLC (“Purelyhosting.com”, “We”, “Us”) and describes how we collect and use the personal information you provide on our web site. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to data or confidential information that is submitted to another person or entity for whom PurelyHosting.com may provide hosting or domain name registration services.

PurelyHosting.com LLC has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.purelyhosting.com](http://www.purelyhosting.com/).

TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at[privacy@PurelyHosting.com](mailto:privacy@PurelyHosting.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

## Information Collection and Use

Personal Information you give us depends on the type of service, support, or sale inquiry, and may include your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, dates of service provided, types of service provided, payment history, manner of payment, amount of payments, date of payments, domain name, credit card or other payment information. The financial information will be transferred only be used to bill you for the products and services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider.

## Information Use

This information is used for billing and to provide service and support to our customers. We may also study this information to determine our customers’ needs and provide support for our customers. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

Additionally, your information may be shared with our affiliates that, with your consent, provide services to you based on links displayed within your CPanel access and control to facilitate your use of additional amenities included with your hosting account.

We may disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to potential partners, our affiliates, and reputable third parties. We take all available measures to select affiliates and service providers that are ethical and provide similar privacy protection to their customers and the community.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Purelyhosting.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

## Access and Choice

If your personally information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, or request deletion of said information by making the change on our user account page, by submitting a help ticket to Customer Support, by emailing us at [privacy@PurelyHosting.com](mailto:privacy@PurelyHosting.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Opt-out Preferences

By default, customers do not receive any voluntary system updates, such as the newsletters, invoices, and mailings. Affiliates will receive periodic promotional emails, but can opt out at any time. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to adjust the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [privacy@PurelyHosting.com](mailto:privacy@PurelyHosting.com). Customers may not opt out of possibly receiving important system notifications, in the rare event that such notification would be necessary.

## Tracking Technologies / Cookies

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small text files – “cookies” – that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on the Purelyhosting.com’s website.

## Analytics / Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site and servers, track access, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and Web browsing.

## Web Beacons / Gifs

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

## Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. PurelyHosting.com uses technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alternation or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control. PurelyHosting.com uses security measures including and not limited to: physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. When we ask customers or users to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Additional Information

## Links to 3rd Party Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Purelyhosting.com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

## Changes To This Policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at [privacy@PurelyHosting.com](mailto:privacy@PurelyHosting.com). PurelyHosting.com has established internal mechanisms to verify its ongoing adherence to its privacy policy and also encourages individuals covered by this privacy policy to raise any concerns about our processing of personal information by contacting PurelyHosting.com at the address below.

Email: [support@purelyhosting.com](mailto:support@purelyhosting.com)  
Phone: 800-509-4206  
605 North High Street #264  
Columbus, OH 43215 USA
